All right. Now that you understand the
different types of variables, we're
going to talk about input and output. In
programming, basically everything
happens by taking some input, doing some
work, and giving back some output. So,
we're going to talk about how to do
input and output. I'm going to show you
two simple types of output and one
simple type of input for the first half
of the course. And we're going to use
those pretty much exclusively for the
first half. After we've learned most of
the do work portion of programming, then
we'll talk more in depth about different
types of input and different types of
output. But to start, we're just going
to keep the input and output simple. So,
I'm going to teach you two outputs, one
input, but just know you could swap them
for any type of input or output in your
program, and your program would work
just about the same. So, some versions
of output, you could maybe send it to a
printer, you could display it on the
screen. Um, there's a lot of different
versions of output. Um, there's a lot of
different versions of input. You could
get input from the keyboard. You could
get input from the mouse. You could get
input from someone talking into a
microphone. All of these different
versions of input can be replaced for
the simple one I'm going to teach you.
Um, but for now we're going to keep it
simple and we're just going to talk
about simple ways of doing input and
simple ways of doing output.